nuclear-coffee.com 2018-12-29

# Privacy policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This Privacy Policy covers how we collect, use, disclose, transfer, and store your information. Please take a moment to get to know our practices and contact us if you have any questions.

This information note is provided in compliance with Personal Data Protection Code and articles 13 and 14 Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016), to those who interact with our web services through electronic access or by using our software.

## Owner and data controller

ONE UP LTD - NO 5, SPATHARIKOU, 4004 MESA GEITONIA, LIMASSOL, CYPRUS  
Owner and data controller contact: [privacy@nuclear.coffee](mailto:privacy@nuclear.coffee)

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

Personal information is data that can be used to uniquely identify or contact a specific individual.  
We do our best not to collect any personal information from you which we will not need in order to provide you with best services.

Here are types of personal information that we collect:

  * When you purchase from us (see details below)
  * When you subscribe to our newsletters, we also ask for your email address
  * When you contact us, e.g. for a technical support request, we may keep a record of your communication

We use the personal information we collect to help us develop, deliver, protect, and improve our products, services, content, and customer communications. We also use it to keep you up to date on our latest product announcements and updates, and to send you important notices, e.g. about changes to our Terms of Service or our Privacy Policy. You may opt out of receiving some of these communications.  
We may also use personal information for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products and services.

### Purchases

If you purchase a license from us via our website the payment will be processed by CleverBridge (our e-commerce provider). CleverBridge provide some data about your purchase to us, such as your name, email, billing address. CleverBridge does NOT provide us with your sensitive payment information, such as credit card information, etc. For more information about CleverBridge privacy policy visit: [CleverBridge Privacy Policy](https://www.cleverbridge.com/corporate/support/privacy-policy)

### License record

If you've purchased a license from us - we will keep some data about a license you purchased in our records. Data we keep in our records ONLY includes:  

  * Your email address
  * Your name
  * Product purchased
  * License key issued to you for activation of our software

We retain this information so that we can resend your license key if you lose it and to verify if you're paying customer of our software. License records are usually held forever since customers often need to re-activate old software. We do not share any of this information with any other parties. License records are stored on our server securely, your license key can only be sent to your email address which you've used during purchase. License records are removed from the database at user's request, if you wish for your license record to be removed, let us know by contacting us at [privacy@nuclear.coffee](mailto:privacy@nuclear.coffee)

### Technical support

We retain all communication (emails you've sent us) between you and our technical support, so that we have a record of our interactions with customer in order to provide you with best technical support.

### Data collected by our desktop software

Our desktop software does NOT collect or send any personal or statistical information.

## Collection and Use of non-personal Information

Non personal information is data that cannot be used to uniquely identify or contact a specific individual. Usually aggregated data for statistical purposes.  
Here are some examples of non-personal information that we collect:  

  * Google analytics (see below)

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to track visitors to our website, which allows us to see information on user website activities including, but not limited to, page views, source, and time spent on our website. This only provides us with aggregate data. We cannot identify individuals from this data. For more information about Google Analytics privacy policy visit: <https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html>

## Cookies and other Technologies

We use “cookies” to collect information about your use of the website. Cookies are small text files a website can store on your hard drive. We use the information we collect in this manner to better understand our users’ interaction with our website and to optimise the user experience. You can disable cookies in your browser settings, but please note that certain features on our website may not be available as a result.

In our email communications, we may use other technologies like “pixel tags” and “click-through URLs” in order to determine if an email has been opened and which links have been clicked. This way, we can determine and improve the effectiveness of our communications. Pixel tags are small images shown inside an HTML email; you can disable tracking by disabling HTML in your email client. A link with a click-through URL, when clicked, first sends the user to a web server which records the click, and then to the link’s destination.

## Protection of Personal Information

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorised access to or unauthorised alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorised access to systems where we store personal data.

Whenever you connect to any of our websites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption for all information that is being transmitted. However, no method of transmitting or storing data is 100% secure, so we cannot guarantee the security of information you transmit to us.

Please note that our servers are located outside of the European Union (in the US), as well as the servers of our partners (e.g. Google). If you use our software or websites, you agree that your information is transmitted, stored, and processed in data centres outside the EU, in most cases in the US.

### Security

Our websites only operate via HTTPS, so our users can be sure that any data transferred remains safe. All connections to our websites are encrypted and authenticated through a strong security protocol.

## Children

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under 13, we will promptly delete this information. Parents or guardians can contact us at [privacy@nuclear.coffee](mailto:privacy@nuclear.coffee)

## 3rd Party Sites and Services

Our websites or any of our services may contain links to third-party websites or services. We are not responsible for the information collected by those third parties and we encourage you to read their privacy policy before submitting any personal information to them.

## Retention time

The Data are kept for the time necessary to provide the service requested by the User, or stated by the purposes outlined in this document, and the User can always request that the Data Controller suspend or remove the data.

## Disclosure to 3rd parties

We don’t share personal information with anyone outside of our company, except for the few exceptions below.

We work together with other companies who provide services to us, like hosting our website, sending out newsletters, analysing our website traffic, hosting our cloud services, etc.. We only share personal information with these companies if it is necessary for them to provide their services. All companies we work with provide at least industry standard systems and processes to ensure the security and confidentiality of your information.

We also share personal information if disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; to enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof; to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud or security issues; and to protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of our company, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If our company is involved in a reorganisation, merger, or sale, the information we collect may be transferred as part of that transaction.

## User's rights

The individuals whom the personal data refer to are always entitled to get confirmation of the existence of such data and to know the contents and origin of same, to verify their accuracy or obtain their integration or updating, or their correction (article 7 of the Personal Data Protection Code, articles 11 and 12 Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016).

In accordance with the above provisions, users are also entitled to obtain the cancellation, transformation in anonymous form or blocking of data processed in breach of the law, as well as, in any event, to oppose their processing for legitimate reasons.  
All requests should be sent to [privacy@nuclear.coffee](mailto:privacy@nuclear.coffee)

## About this Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. When we change the policy, we will post the changes on this page, and, if the policy changes in a significant way, we will also provide a prominent notice (e.g. on our website). If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@nuclear.coffee](mailto:privacy@nuclear.coffee).

Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted here. This policy is dated May 24, 2018.
